Now, it's your turn.
次はみなさんの番です
You're going to get the chance to practice some additional questions yourself.
ここでは、追加の質問に対する答え方を練習します
They're similar to those you may be asked in an autonomous systems interview.
これらの質問は、自律システム関連の面接に出る可能性があるものと似ています
Well, you split out the questions in a different job areas like the interviews were.
面接と同じく、質問は職種ごとに分かれています
While for the project, you only need to focus on
プロジェクトの場合は、特定の分野に的を絞り
a specific area as well as discuss one of your own projects you've worked on.
自分が手掛けたプロジェクトのひとつについて説明します
Feel free to check out some of the questions in
さらに練習したい方は、他のセクションにある
other sections on your own traditional practice.
質問もチェックしてみてください
Please remember that this list is not meant to be exhaustive.
このリストはすべてを網羅するものではありません
There are many, many more potential questions in
面接で訊かれる可能性のある専門分野の質問は
these areas that you could be asked during your interview.
他にもまだまだたくさんあります
However, just like the interviews you watched before,
ただし、前にご覧いただいた面接と同様
these are meant to be generally indicative of
ここで紹介するのは、出題される可能性がある
the type and style of questions might be asked.
質問の種類・形式です
As such, the questions are meant to help you think through how you
そのため、これらの質問は、この種の質問や練習にどのように
would approach questions of this style and practice, how to do so.
取り組むべきか、またその方法を検討する上で活用してください
In answering these questions,
質問に答える際には
make sure to add any code, drawings,
説明に必要と思われる
or diagrams you feel are necessary to explain yourself.
コードや描画、図を必ず加えてください
For the project, any code you write should be done in C++.
プロジェクトでは、コードは C++ で記述してください
While you go through your questions,
質問を確認する際に
there is one additional item to consider.
考慮すべき点がもう 1 つあります
You likely have not finished a topic just by answering the first question asked to be.
それは、最初の質問に答えてもトピックを終えたことにはならないということです
After your initial answer,
最初の質問に答えると
your interviewer will likely follow-up on different items you mentioned,
おそらく面接官はあなたが述べた別の項目について質問を続けたり
as well as probe deeper to see just how far your knowledge on a particular topic goes.
特定のトピックについてどの程度の知識があるか探ろうとします
As such, you should build this into your responses in
ですので、プロジェクトの質問に答える際にはこの点を踏まえ
your project as you answer what do you think some of the likely follow-ups are,
次にどんな質問が続く可能性があるか
how might you even go deeper than the initial question required.
最初の質問よりもさらに深く掘り下げるにはどうすればいいかを検討してください
You may run into things you don't know.
知らない問題が出る可能性もあります
If you're unfamiliar with the question in your area,
該当分野の質問で馴染みのないものがあれば
go read up and learn about the topic.
学習して、そのトピックの知識を得ておいてください
It's okay if you don't know every single item in here,
ここにあるすべての項目を知っておく必要はありません
and it's fine to make part of this course a learning experience in
関心分野における学習体験や面接準備の一環として
your area of interest as well as interview preparation.
このコースを捉えていただいてもかまいません
We encourage you to challenge yourself here.
大切なのは、自分に挑戦することです
Don't just stick to questions you feel you can easily answer.
簡単に答えられると思う質問にばかり取り組まないでください
You might even find a couple of items you want to work on to add to your portfolio.
自分のポートフォリオに追加するために取り組みたい項目が見つかるかもしれません
After the project, we hope you feel much more confident about
プロジェクト終了後には、さらに自信をもってこれらの質問に答え
answering these types of questions and interviewing for autonomous systems positions.
自律システム関連の面接に挑むことができるはずです
Good luck in your job search.
それではみなさん、頑張ってください